This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop!
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far!
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home!
I'm
so truly grateful!
I ran into you on that day so long ago!
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes!
Till we knew we weren't alone!
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way!
And with it I know we'll rise!
We'll be flying up high!
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon,
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I want to take you to?
Let's head for it then!
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But after the wave, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
Chop Chop Chop Chop.
By the way, do you ever read the W .E .J.?
The World Economic Journal?
It's a major paper, Lili.
Everyone knows it.
They used to run this awesome comic strip.
It was called Saru, Warrior of the Sea.
Had a giant robot and everything.
I wouldn't miss it for my life, Lili.
Saru was this hero who
could walk on water.
He had a transforming robot
and a little Skull pal, too.
And the bad guys, the evil armies of Germa
double six, enemies to all marines, Lili.
People all over the world love that comic.
I know it looks like a kid's story on
the surface, but from what I heard,
it was actually based on true reports
from the big shot Navy heroes, Lili.
So it's pretty much propaganda,
teaching the little kiddies that the Navy
is always right and always wins the day,
Lili. Lo, lo, lo.
So why would a guy like me read
a comic like that, you ask?
Why for the villains!
For Germa double six!
Their armies used every dirty trick in
the book to try and pull one over on Saru.
They were a role model
for outlaws like me.
Anyway,
I get that Germa has to lose
for the sake of the story,
but I always cheered for them.
You guys are the best!
Don't tell me that!
I've got nothing to do
with them, you know.
I'm telling you as a fan in fact I could
hardly wait to meet the
rest of your family.
Little then fanboy over them
instead—are you
gonna open or not?
So
as I was just saying, would
you stop following me?
This is my room, you weirdo.
It's supposed to be my room
too, so why am I in a cage?
I am a genius scientist.
I deserve better treatment than this.
You've been crying about
this all day, Lili.
Listen, we were told to
capture you, not pamper you.
But Sanji here—he's the
groom that's gonna bring the
Vinsmoke family and the
Charlotte family together as one.
So you may be a genius,
but he's still worth more.
worth more
Yeah, I'm not getting married.
I told you get the hell out of here.
What did you just say?
Ain't nobody disrespects my boy Vito.
Now apologize for your dead meat!
He didn't hurt my feelings at all.
I mean thanks for
sticking up for me buddy.
Yeah, but he was just playing around
No, I was serious.
Both of you, get the hell out
of my room right now. Again?
I heard that.
Oh, it is on now!
Hey, you don't do it!
Insult me, but don't insult my friends.
I'll kill you!
We're trying to be pals here.
Let it go, Lili.
Don't bother.
I hate your guts.
And if you don't leave, I've
got more insults for you.
You son of a...
Got it!
What the hell are you trying to pull?
I'm sorry, ma 'am.
Kaido, you do realize that he's one
of the Vinsmoke family, don't you?
If you lay so much as a finger on him,
then my veggie's head is gonna roll.
Do you understand me? Ha!
Though while we're at it, maybe I should
lop your head off first, you dumb-o.
Get out of here!
I'll be nice from now on, I promise!
I promise!
Hey, are you...
I'm sorry, ma 'am.
It won't happen again.
With punishment, there's
no dinner for you tonight.
Please, anything but that!
Yo, Lili, sorry to bother you.
We can talk about Janet later, Lili.
Not happening.
I know that face.
But I can't remember where.
Alright, I was wrong.
I'm gonna die after all.
It's so hot.
I might melt before I starve.
I want Saji back on the show.
I just need some ice cream.
I wish I could take off my fur.
It's not helping right now.
I know the feeling.
Minx have a low tolerance for heat.
If I can't cool off soon, I fear
I'm going to become a mummy.
Wait, a mummy?
Hold on a second.
That's a big deal.
Hey, Nami.
If I become a mommy, that would
be like an upgrade for me.
I don't care.
If I had a fancy sarcophagus,
then could I see your panties?
I wish I had the strength to slap you.
Mommy, I'm hungry and
it's hot and I'm tired.
I need some nutrition.
We've had such bad luck.
It's been too stormy
for us to fish at all.
Now the sun's killing us.
I know it's hot, but please catch
something while we still have clear skies.
Otherwise, we'll all starve to
death before we even get there.
Oh, team food!
We're giving it our best, but, uh...
It's actually so hot that
the water is boiling.
What?
So, uh, that's a no on the fish, then?
What should we do?
Huh?
Emergency rations.
Don't look at me like that!
Wolf! Pull! Quick!
It's huge!
I don't want you...
Freddy, help!
I'm all cheering for you.
Come on, Luffy, keep fighting!
So, we might not die?
I got you, Fischity!
You did it!
Finally!
Yeah, that should be quite the feast.
Let's eat!
You're going in my belly!
Yeah, that color is a bad sign.
Might be poisonous.
It's a fish that eats food!
You don't know what you're talking about!
Just wait one second.
I can look it up before we cook it.
Not with the saucy ladies already.
I want an encyclopedia of fish!
Got it!
Okay. Let's see.
Not this one. Oh, come on. Please.
Yes!
You can't eat the skin of that fish!
It's poisonous!
Extremely poisonous!
Sanji made a note about it in here!
Wow, the skin's so good!
I know that you're hungry,
but wait for me to grill it!
Here, Kara, you should try
some, too! I don't know.
It's awfully slimy. Luffy!
Okay, dinner's served!
Why, that's music to my
ears! I'm famished. Eat out!
Mmm, it's so good!
You're an awesome cook, Nami!
Oh, the tears, they won't stop!
I feel so alive! Thank you!
Such joy!
I just followed Sanji's
recipe, so don't thank me!
Chopper, eat something
before you pass out!
Here, take it.
Boobie's doing bad.
I'm afraid he's gonna die.
I'm so, so cold, Chopper. Help me.
Crying isn't gonna save him.
Have some fish to get
that brain working again,
and I know you'll come up
with a plan to fix this.
Now here, eat up.
But even if I can't stop
crying, it's no use.
I already used up all of our antidotes.
Yum.
We gotta find an island, Nami.
I don't want him to die.
Is that food?
Damn it.
Why isn't it easier to find land?
I looked at Sanji's notes myself,
and according to his book,
the poison from the skin
should kill you right away.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
But he didn't react at all till now.
And even though he's
sick, he's still not dead.
Maybe we should have more
faith in Luffy's vitality.
I guess, but look at him.
Yum.
Are you, Tia, gonna die?
The river, it's so beautiful.
Guys, he's at the river stand!
We're about to enter Mama's
territory any moment now. Huh?
First,
we'll run into a bunch
of smaller islands with
the defense network
surrounding Whole Cake Island.
Since there's no reason for Blackleg and
his little entourage to get held up there,
he's probably reached
Whole Cake Island already.
No matter what, don't lower your guard.
I'll go keep a lookout.
I had planned to stop at
the first island ahead.
We can find an antidote there.
What the?
It was hot and now it's snowing?
Pretty.
Hold on.
That's not snow.
Are those sugar clouds? Yep.
We call this a cotton candy flurry.
Cotton candy!
What are you doing here?
Yummy!
What's that?
We're giving a call? Not exactly.
What you're hearing is a warning signal.
That is to say,
We've entered Mama's territory, and
her troops are going to know about it.
I'm getting it!
Hider, disguise yourselves as something!
I'm trying to help you! Yeah!
Are you ignoring me?
I see something! Pec-Oms!
It's a ship!
It's coming right for us!
What?
How did they get here so fast?
Who is they?
It's called the Tart.
They're one of Mama's scout ships.
Great.
I can't make it out through the fog.
What should we do?
You go hide.
I'll handle this mess somehow.
Works for me. This is bad.
I think Ubi's condition is getting worse.
The poison is spreading.
I don't know if he can hold on much
longer without some kind of treatment.
Do you think they'll have
something on the scout ship?
Alas, but you've got to
hide right now! Okay!
Come on, Chopper, double time!
Oh, my God.
I'm in there.
Is that a transponder, snail?
It's huge!
I wonder what that number could mean.
Sixty-six.
This is Germa.
Is that Straw Hat Luffy's ship?
Just don't look, it's Germa Double Six!
So it's not Big Mom after all.
They call Germa Double Six the warmongers.
What business do you have in these waters?
Answer, quickly!
We're about to hit their ship!
We're on the sails!
Hurry!
Lucy, I'll be back.
Seems we avoided a crash, at least.
Sanji!
That curly eyebrow! No!
It must be him! What? Really? We did it?
Sanji!
I can't believe we found you!
And I can't believe that
we found Sanji so quickly!
Quite the coincidence.
Hey, Sanji, we have a problem!
Luffy ate some poisoned
fish and he's dying!
Do you have an antidote
on that big ship, maybe?
It's urgent!
Wait, can't you hear me? Sanji!
You got the wrong guy.
Well, I guess we might look alike.
But my name is Yonji.
Yonji?
But he's got curly eyebrows, though.
If he's not Sanji, then
who in the heck's Yonji?
My relationship with your associate
Sanji is a highly classified matter.
It's a secret that I'll
take to the grave with me.
That's his younger brother for sure.
Wonder who else is in his family.
How do you know they're related?
I don't get it.
Cutie!
Are you saying that, Sanji?
Yonji, sir.
Not to interrupt, but I don't think
we'll find Master Sanji on that ship.
It seems we missed each
other on the way here.
So it would appear.
Let's pull back, then.
This was a waste of time.
Hey, come back! Sanji!
I'm Yonji!
Oh, no! Luffy!
He's developing a rash.
He can't fight it anymore.
I know Luffy has strong antibodies, so
this poison must be really powerful.
Stay with us, please.
It's just a poison from
a stupid fish, right?
If you're going to be king of
the pirates, then fight back.
She's right.
You can't die now.
Don't give up.
You gotta help us.
We used all of our antidotes on him, but
his condition just keeps getting worse.
You must have something, right?
I'm begging you!
If nothing else, can you
do it for Sanji at least?
Don't let your brother's captain die!
Sorry, guys.
I'm not into the whole saving lives thing.
But if you want that medicine so
bad, why don't you take it from us?
You guys are pirates, aren't you?
He only has Sanji's bad parts
and none of the good ones!
He's a playboy jerk!
Why are you, Tia, being so cruel?
Just say the word and he's dead.
Yunji. Huh?
Stop being so stinging, will you?
Don't you, sir!
What is going on?
Luffy!
Lady Major!
Hang in there!
Don't die!
Luffy! No!
Who are you, Pia? An enemy?
Do forgive him.
He's rather heartless.
A creep, too.
But never mind, my little brother.
I'll set this straight.
Your little brother?
Are you related to Sanji?
She's got curly eyebrows, too!
She's lovely!
Thank you!
He flies? Damn it!
What were you thinking
humiliating me like that?
Buffoon, you should be
ashamed of yourself.
Oh, I wonder how he's floating.
It's technology. Huh?
They're powerful, don't get me wrong.
but the strength of
German double six is the
strength of science you
might call them a scientific
fighting squad that's
why mama's interested
she wants that technology
for herself back homes
that name rings a bell
if I recall Vinsmoke was
the name of a royal
family many years ago they
conquered the north blue
i believe and they did
so with an overwhelming
show of military might
royalty like vivi or like neptune's family
so they're actually
really famous that's right
their name was synonymous
with evil in fact
in a comic strip they
were used as villains i'm
impressed.
You're a regular historian.
I've been alive for a long time.
And dead as well.
You see, it's not just a story.
For even still, we are royalty.
Germa is a nation without soil.
We own no territory, but we are given the
right to attend the reverie all the same.
I see.
Then I beg your pardon.
May I see your royal panties?
Most honored lady?
Stop it!
Now, if you don't mind, I'll
be taking that from him.
I'm going to guess he ate the skin of an
armored stonefish from the boiling sea.
Yeah, but how did you know?
This poison has very particular effects.
He's quite the glutton.
Even a giant wouldn't survive this.
What?
We can't save him?
But there has to be some way!
I fail!
I'm the worst doctor in the world!
But this is good.
You're lucky.
It's my favorite.
This poison is the best.
What are you doing?
Down the hatch.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
If you suck out that
poison, you'll die for sure!
Oh, I'm so jealous!
If only I could trade places with him!
Though, alas, my lips are long gone!
The rash is transferring?
There's no more rash.
It's all gone.
You sucked it out.
Are you okay?
Never felt better,
because I'm Poison Pink.
Is that a code name?
Mm-hmm, delicious. Whoa!
Whoa, what happened?
Bluefeet!
You're okay!
I was so scared!
I thought you had got her for sure!
I'm so happy!
Luffy!
Wait, did I fall asleep while
I was eating that giant fish?
The skin part was really
good! Is there any left? No!
You don't remember?
Soji!
That's a woman!
Actually, you're right.
Luffy, she's the person
who just saved your life.
Huh?
Thanks, lady.
She what?
So that's the infamous Straw Hat Luffy.
I see. Cool.
I never knew Sanji had a big sister.
Yes.
That's right.
Sanji is a Vinsmoke like us.
He was separated from
us when he was young.
Our father's been searching
for him for a while.
About two years ago, when Sanji's
wanted poster was first circulated,
My father personally requested that
the Navy make catching him a priority.
Sadly, they pursued a man
named Devil by mistake.
Devil?
He's the guy from the Flying Fish Riders.
We met him right before
we went to Sabaody.
Ah, Sanji was not a
fan of that whole mess.
It wasn't until recently that the
government finally ironed things out.
When your crew made
your surprise comeback,
they captured an image of
Sanji during the chaos.
Afterwards, they gave us a
call to share the good news.
Of course, our father raised
Sanji's bounty immediately.
As for the dead or
alive, that was no good.
So it was changed to
say only alive instead.
So that's why.
We knew there was something behind
that, but we couldn't figure it out.
Okay so where's Sanji right now?
Can't say he could be with Big Mom
or he could be with our father.
We thought we might catch him on
the way, but we were too late.
Well we'll see him at the tea party,
and that's the important part!
They won't be long now,
and I even got to meet you?
You took good care of Sanji for that.
I'm grateful
Sanji sister
Thanks for saving my
life for real, but still
We're taking Sanjuvac.
He's my Gourmet, my friend.
I won't give up on him!
So, dumb.
Don't save your enemy's life.
Hey, you!
You're Peckham's from the
Big Mom Pirates, right?
So what the hell are you doing
hanging out with the Straw Hats?
I have my reasons, and
that's all I'm gonna say.
I got no obligation to
explain it to you get out
Things might be different after this
wedding ceremony, but right now.
You're just some random guy.
I can't argue with that
For the time being, at least now,
pretend this meeting never happened.
Good call—our mistake for
butting in, if you ask me.
We don't want to cause any trouble
and put the wedding in jeopardy.
jeopardy
I'd recommend you tread lightly as well.
You do have some sense! Get on!
Raise the anchor. Let's move.
Good luck.
I'll be seeing you.
They ran into Germa, but it
seems they avoided a fight.
Yeah, I'm sure it's their ship.
I can confirm that Straw
Hat Luffy is on board, too.
What's next?
Jinbei...